Today I was going to do more synonyms.
Many ask for synonyms.
And today I was going to take a very common word that we use every day.
And that's the word go.
There are many synonyms for the word go.
stroll
Then you go.
You go a bit without definite goals.
You can have some nice clothes.
Man stroller,
You could say that you stroll on the town in the fine weather.
A synonym to flan is spattered.
Then you are also out and about.
You walk like town, a little planless you go.
You can be out walking.
Then you are out to go, to get some exercise maybe
You walk.
You go out for a walk.
You roam the meadow.
You roam in the forest.
You can take a walk.
A pretty fun expression is that you can call your legs and feet for apostle horses.
Then you can say that you use
Used is a word (a synonym) for used
The apostle horses are used.
You could say that you should take a little round.
Now I'm going to take a little round.
Wind, I'm going out and moping.
Then you are also out and about.
You can call your legs the pans.
You touch the pans.
No, now I have to go out and touch the pans.
Now I have been sitting still for too long.
You can squeeze, go out and knuckle.
There were a lot of synonyms to go.
I hope you start using synonyms.
It is fun with synonyms.
It enriches the language with synonyms.
It may be good to look up the words to get them in the right context.
One can look up the "used apostle horses"
Then you can see in what contexts exactly that expression stands.
The important thing is that you start to own the new words, that you use them so that they become yours.
So that you own the words.
And become active in your vocabulary.
Synonyms are fun.